# Alyssa C. Kieffer

Greater Philadelphia Area | **C**: (302) 753-6006 | **E**: <a href="mailto:thealphia.com/in/ackieffer/">thealyssanet@gmail.com</a> **LinkedIn:** <a href="mailto:www.linkedin.com/in/ackieffer/">www.linkedin.com/in/ackieffer/</a> | **Portfolio**: <a href="mailto:alykief.github.io/alyssanet/">alykief.github.io/alyssanet/</a>

### **Profile**

Web Developer with a long history of managerial experience, and proven self-motivation proven by years of remote work success. Exceptional organizational, time management, leadership and adaptability skills with an outgoing, creative personality that shines through as an asset in the work place.

## **Skills**

Experienced in Data Entry, HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Express/EJS, Node, Mongo/Mongoose, Angular, SQL, REACT and Ruby on Rails. Has worked hands-on with Amazon, Salesforce, Concur and Quickbooks, along with all outlets of Microsoft Office. Adequate knowledge of Adobe Photoshop, Social Media Marketing and Branding.

# Experience

#### Web Development & Graphic Design, Freelancer

2018 - Current

Connected with multiple companies to design and restyle websites, create for-print marketing material along with digital graphics for social media and e-mail chains. Specifically, created a scheduled bi-weekly eBlast with graphics & original content for a large aesthetic company in order to target their audience and promote new releases along with upcoming events.

#### **S&D Kids, Office Manager**

2013 - 2018

Worked closely with President to create a CMS system that would better suit the demands of growing business & staff, tweaked the inventory system in order to keep up with influxes of orders throughout the busy season and helped make a more aesthetically pleasing & user-friendly website. Trained all new hires to list items on third-party retail sites along with the company's own website. Assisted in Branding and Social Media Marketing when the company launched their own brand sold on third-party retail websites, including logo design. Worked on the back-end of Amazon Marketplace in order to list thousands of new items, while also fixing the styling of existing pages. Placed orders for new inventory, budgeted, and worked with P.O.'s to create a system to list items before they were received to help with the busy season. Worked remotely for 2-years with great success.

#### **ACK Photography**

2011 - 2018

Wedding and family photographer with great knowledge of DSLR cameras and Adobe Photoshop capabilities. 40 hours of Photography classes at Wilmington University

## **Education**

#### **General Assembly**

Web Development Immersive Remote | 2018

3-month program in which multiple code languages were covered and multiple projects completed. Basis of CSS, Python and HTML were already had, but acquired extensive knowledge of Javascript (SQL, MongoDB, Express.js, AngularJS, Node.js, jQuery, React.js) & Ruby (specifically, Ruby on Rails) thanks to this course. Worked with GitHub, Zoom and Slack and had experience working on group projects remotely with highly praised outcomes. Self-motivated to do homework in a timely fashion and went above and beyond to reach stretch goals throughout the course. Practiced exceptional time management in order to balance life and a very demanding course load. Excelled at CSS styling and MEAN stack.

## Wilmington University

Associates in Liberal Studies | 2018

Degree acquired with a remote program, which again required great organizational skills. Double Minor in Photography & Graphic Design. Member of the Photography Club and Computer Guru Group. Completed program with a 3.0 GPA and Dean's List in 2018 while holding a full-time job.